在创建自定义视图的最后一步就是增加interactivity
The final step in your custom view creation
你可以监听用户输入事件，包括
is adding interactivity. You can listen for user
按键，轨迹球的移动，
input events including key presses, trackball movement, and
还有更重要的是，屏幕触摸事件
most importantly, screen touch events, all by overriding the
这些都是通过重载相应的事件处理程序实现的，Android支持多达
corresponding event handlers. Android supports tracking of up
11个接触点的追踪，我们
to 11 individual contact points in what we
称之为“爵士手”模式，它可以
like to call, jazz hands mode which enables
使你完成复杂的多指互动模式
you to complete complex and multi-finger interaction models. Now,
而对于风向来说，现在这里没有互动的需求
there's really no interaction required for a wind gauge, but
但是你可以通过查阅那些描述
you can find out more about handling input events by checking
如何创建应用的完全互动视图的文档
the motion event docs or the developer guide describing how to
或者开发者指南得知更多有关处理输入事件的知识，
create your own, fully interactive custom views, both from the [UNKNOWN]
现在，不要让这个新发现的力量迷昏了头脑
below. Now, be careful not to let this new found power
因为你的用户永远不会遇到
go to your head. By definition, your users will have never
你使用的新控件，所以学习如何使用它就是
encountered your brand spanking new control. So learning how to use
将使你的应用使用起来更爱不释手
it is going to add friction to the use of your app.
最起码，它应该和系统中的其他部分表现一致
At the very least, it should behave consistently with the rest of the system
并且你应该避免自己创建系统控件
and you should avoid creating your own
如果它看起来像
versions of system controls. If it looks kind of
一个按钮，工作起来也像一个按钮，那你或许应该继续使用一个
like a button and works kind of like a button, you should probably just go ahead
按钮，但我认为这是不符合逻辑的即使它已经持续了很长时间了
and use a button, but I think this non sequitur has gone on long enough.